Guide to the Clesson Nathan Turner papers, [ca. 1926]-1987.
Turner, Clesson Nathan papers, [ca. 1926]-1987.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Clesson Nathan Turner papers, [ca. 1926]-1987.
21-11-810
Turner, Clesson Nathan 1908-.
14 cubic ft.
Notes, correspondence, reports, bulletins, articles and photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Materials relating to Turner's career as professor and agricultural engineer.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Agricultural Engineering.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes reports and minutes of the New York Farm Electrification Council and notes, data and correspondence pertaining to bulk milk cooling and other projects; correspondence concerning the work of the Council, agricultural engineering, and the installation and operation of electrically powered farm equipment, as well as correspondence and material concerning the American Society of Agricultural Engineers; reports, bulletins, articles, and addresses by Turner and others concerning the use of electricity on the farm, with related photographs. Also, notes on tile drainage and material for his course Agricultural Engineering 101.
Also, paper on "The Poole Electric Clock," by Professor Turner, 1987, published in the Bulletin of the National Association of Watch and Clock Collectors, Inc., August 1988.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Turner, Clesson Nathan,1908-.; American Society of Agricultural Engineers.; New York Farm Electrification Council.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Agricultural Engineering.
Subjects:
Agricultural engineering.; Dairy engineering.; Drain-tiles.; Drainage.; Electricity in agriculture.; Farm equipment.; Milk tanks.; Milk--Cooling--Equipment and supplies.; Rural electrification.; Agricultural engineers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Appendix to Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Progress Report - New York Farm Electrification Council, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Minutes, 1935-45 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Minutes, 1946-48 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Minutes, 1949-52 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Executive Committee Minutes, 1947-51 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Alphabetical File, A (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Alphabetical File, B (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Alphabetical File, BE (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Alphabetical File, BO (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Niagara Electric Corporation (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Alphabetical File, C (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corporation (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Central New York Power Corporation (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Alphabetical File, CI (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Alphabetical File, CR (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Alphabetical File, D (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Alphabetical File, DI (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Executive Committee (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Alphabetical File, F (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Alphabetical File, G (Box 3, Folder 15)
- General Electric Company (Box 3, Folder 16)
- G.L.F. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Alphabetical File, GO (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Alphabetical File, H (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Alphabetical File, HE (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Alphabetical File, HO (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Alphabetical File, I (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Alphabetical File, J (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Alphabetical File, K (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Alphabetical File, KI (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Alphabetical File, L (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Alphabetical File, LI (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Long Island Lighting Company (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Lyron Rural Electric Company (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Alphabetical File, Mc (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Alphabetical File, M (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Alphabetical File, MO (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Alphabetical File, N (Box 4, Folder 1)
- New York Power and Light Corporation (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Niagara Hudson Power Corporation (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Niagara, Lockport & Ontario Power Company (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Alphabetical File, O (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Alphabetical File, P (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Alphabetical File, Q (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Alphabetical File, R (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Alphabetical File, RO (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Rochester Gas & Electric Corporation (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Rockland Light & Power Company (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Alphabetical File, S (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Alphabetical File, SE (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Alphabetical File, SM (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Alphabetical File, ST (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Alphabetical File, T (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Alphabetical File, UV (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Alphabetical File, W (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Alphabetical File, WH (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Alphabetical File, XYZ (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Correspondence (from Turner), 1939-45 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Correspondence (from Turner), 1946-51 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Business Correspondence, 1925-47 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Business Correspondence, 1948-60 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Alphabetical File, A (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Engineering Department (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Alphabetical File, B (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Alphabetical File, C (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corporation (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Alphabetical File, D (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Alphabetical File, E (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Alphabetical File, F (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Alphabetical File, G (Box 5, Folder 9)
- General Electric Company (Box 5, Folder 10)
- G.L.F. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Alphabetical File, H (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Alphabetical File, I (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Alphabetical File, J (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Alphabetical File, K (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Alphabetical File, L (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Long Island Lighting Company (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Alphabetical File, M (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Maine, University Of (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Alphabetical File, N (Box 5, Folder 20)
- New York State Electric & Gas Corporation (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation - (Western Division) Formerly Buffalo Niagara Electric Company (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation - (Central Division) Formerly Central New York Power Corporation (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation - (Eastern Division) Formerly New York Power & Light (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Niagara Hudson Power Corporation (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Alphabetical File, O (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Operating Committee (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Alphabetical File, P (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Alphabetical File, R (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Rochester Gas & Electric Corporation (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Rockland Light & Power Corporation (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Alphabetical File, S (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Alphabetical File, T (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Alphabetical File, UV (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Alphabetical File, W-Z (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Alphabetical File, A (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Agricultural Engineering Department (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Alphabetical File, B (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Alphabetical File, C (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corporation (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Alphabetical File, D (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Alphabetical File, E (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Executive Committee (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Electricity on the Farm (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Alphabetical File, F (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Alphabetical File, G (Box 5, Folder 46)
- General Electric Company (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Alphabetical File, H (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Alphabetical File, I (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Alphabetical File, J (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Alphabetical File, K (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Alphabetical File, L (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Long Island Lighting Company (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Alphabetical File, M (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Maine, University of (Box 5, Folder 55)
- University of Michigan (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Alphabetical File, N (Box 5, Folder 57)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation (Central Division) (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation (Eastern Division) (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation (Western Division) (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Alphabetical File, O (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Operating Committee (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Operating Committee (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Alphabetical File, P (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Pennsylvania State University (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Alphabetical File, R (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Rochester Gas & Electric Corporation (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Alphabetical File, S (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Alphabetical File, T (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Alphabetical File, U-V (Box 5, Folder 71)
- USDA (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Alphabetical File, W-Z (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Alphabetical File, A (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Engineering Department (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Alphabetical File, Ba-Bh (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Alphabetical File, Bi-Brn (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Alphabetical File, Bro-Bz (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Alphabetical File, Ca-Cn (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Central Hudson Gas & Electric (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Alphabetical File, Co-Cz (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Craft (Geo. Crowther), 1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Alphabetical File, D (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Alphabetical File, E (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Edison Electric Institute (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Electricity On the Farm (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Executive Committee (Extra Copies etc.), 1955-58 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Alphabetical File, F (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Farm and Home Week, Mar. 1956 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Alphabetical File, Ga-Gn (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Girton (Box 6, Folder 18)
- General Electric Company (Box 6, Folder 19)
- G.L.F. (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Alphabetical File, Go-Gz (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Alphabetical File, Ha-Hd (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Hampden Engineering Corporation (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Alphabetical File, He-Hn (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Alphabetical File, Ho-Hz (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Alphabetical File, I (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Inter Industry Farm Electric Utilization Council (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Iowa State College (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Alphabetical File, J (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Alphabetical File, K (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Alphabetical File, La-Lh (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Library (Agriculture) (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Long Island Lighting Company (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Alphabetical File, Li-Lz (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Alphabetical File, Ma-Md (Box 6, Folder 35)
- University of Maine (Box 6, Folder 37)
- University of Maryland (Box 6, Folder 38)
- University of Michigan (Box 6, Folder 39)
- University of Minnesota (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Alphabetical File, Me-Mn (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Alphabetical File, Mo-Mz (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Alphabetical File, Mc (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Alphabetical File, N (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Newspapers (Box 6, Folder 45)
- New York State Electric & Gas (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation (Central Division) (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation (Eastern Division) (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation (Western Division) (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Alphabetical File, O (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Oneida-Madsion Electric Cooperative, Incorporated (Blaine Stockton) (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Operating Committee (extra copies etc.), 1955-58 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Orange & Rockland Utilities - Formerly Rockland Light & Power (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Alphabetical File, Pa-Ph (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Alphabetical File, Pi-Pz (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Pennsylvania State University (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Alphabetical File, Q (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Ra-Rn 28 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Rochester Gas & Electric Corp. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Rockland Light & Power Company (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Ro-Rz 29 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Sa-Sd 30 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Se-Sm 31 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Sn-Sth 32 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Sti-Sz 33 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- T 34 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- U.S.D.A (Box 7, Folder 10)
- U 35 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- V 36 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Wa-Wg 37 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- W.G.Y (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Westinghouse (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Wh-Wz 38 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- X-Y 39 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Z 40 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- A 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Engineering Dept. Extension (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Aerovent Fan Company (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Engineering Dept. (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Ba-Bn 2 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Ca-Cn 5 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Central Hudson Gas & Electric (Box 7, Folder 25)
- County Agents (Box 7, Folder 26)
- D 7 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- E 8 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Executive Committee 1957 (extra Copies Etc.) (Box 7, Folder 29)
- F 9 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Ga-Gn 10 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Go-Gz 11 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Ha-Hd 12 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- I 15 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- J 16 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- K 17 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- La-Lh 18 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Long Island Lighting co. (Box 7, Folder 38)
- University of Michigan (Box 7, Folder 39)
- University of Minnesota (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Ma- Md 20 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- N 23 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- New York State Electric & Gas (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. (Central Division) (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. (Eastern Division) (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. (Western Division) (Box 7, Folder 46)
- O 24 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Orange & Rockland Utilities (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Oneida Madsion Electric Cooperative (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Operating Committee, 1957-58 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Pa-Ph 25 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Ra-Rn 28 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Rochester Gas & Electric (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Sa-Sd 30 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- T 34 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- U 35 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- U.S.D.A (Box 7, Folder 57)
- V 36 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Wa-Wg 37 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Agricultural Engineering Monthly Activity Rep. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Engineering 101 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- AG Engineering 101 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Subject Matter Class For AG Engineering (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Kelsey Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Retirement Party, Jennings and Wright (Box 8, Folder 6)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers (Box 8, Folder 7)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers Research Notes (Box 8, Folder 8)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers Programs And Business of Society (Box 8, Folder 9)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers (Box 8, Folder 10)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers: North Atlantic Section: Rural Elec., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers, Aug. 1951 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers, Aug. 1951 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Drainage (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Annual Farm Electrification Conference, 1946-47 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Annual Farm Electrification Conference, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Annual Farm Electrification Conference, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- History of Farm Electrification (Box 8, Folder 18)
- History of Farm Electrification (Box 8, Folder 19)
- History of Farm Electrification (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Plans for the 50-year celebration (Box 8, Folder 21)
- National Farm Electrification (Box 8, Folder 22)
- National Farm Electrification (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Hay analysis (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Hay Sampling Committee (Box 8, Folder 25)
- F.A. Smith Fan (Box 8, Folder 26)
- American Society Of Agricultural Engineers hay questionnaire (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Hay Drier Design Data, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Barn Hay Curing Study, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Hay Drying Data, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Warren Farm Hay (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Heated Air Corps Driers (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Hay Drying (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Forms, Lists, Graphs, Diagrams, & Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 34-37)
- Baird Farm (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Orlo Briggs (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Myron Brookfield (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Brundage Farms (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Brundage Farm (Box 9, Folder 5)
- J.M. Burdick (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Norman Carls (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Ethan M. Clark (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Albert Fonda (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Grant Goodrich (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Hugh Hansen (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Huff Farm Drier (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Furman Huff (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Alton McDuffie (Box 9, Folder 14)
- William Miller (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Moffet Farm Drier (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Edward Nortier (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Cyrus Packard (Box 9, Folder 18)
- H.D. Robinson (Box 9, Folder 19)
- B.B. Robb (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Fredrick P. Stephan (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Donald Stacy (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Filing Reference Sheets (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Publication Lists (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Publication Lists (Box 9, Folder 25)
- History of New York State Agriculture (11.45) (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Farmer Uses (Corn Cutter, Sheller, Crusher) 11.4523 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Freezing Protection - 11.4563 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Freezing Protection - 11.4563 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Soil Sterilization 11.4565 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Plant Growth 11.4566 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Chick & Animal Brooding 11.4568 (Box 9, Folder 32-35)
- Reports, 1925-1943 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Reports, 1944-45 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Reports, 1946-1959 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Reports: Undated (Box 9, Folder 39-42)
- R.E.A.:Census Data (Box 9, Folder 43)
- R.E.A.:Census Data (Box 9, Folder 44)
- USDA (Box 9, Folder 45)
- USDA Farm Elec. Survey Attendance Record (Box 9, Folder 46)
- USDA Farm Elec. Survey (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Bennett's Water Heater Data (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- Data on Water Heater Test: Turner & Tudi (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Hot Water Requirements - Part 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Hot Water Requirements - Part 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Hot Water Requirements - Part 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- G.L.F. Milk Cooler Study, 1937-38 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Morris H. Lloyd (Box 10, Folder 8)
- High Wattage Heaters - K. Bennett (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Cornell Bulletins (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Water Heating - West Penn Power (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Untitled (Box 10, Folder 12)
- R.P. March A-14, X2832 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Charts? (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Untitled (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Letters - Chemical Companies (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Oswego, NY (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Morris Mecklenburg (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Untitled (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Bulk Milk Cooling in Six States (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Field Study: Maine (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Field Study: Michigan (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Field Study: Wisconsin (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Field Study: Indiana (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Field Study: Minnesota (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Furnas Electric Company (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Survey: Operating Services & Difficulties, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Sunset Bulk Cooler Tests (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Performance Tests For New York States (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Control Panels Wiring Diagrams (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Cornell Reports on Bulk Milk Cooling (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Craft Bulk Cooler Tests, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Girton Manufacturing Company (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Research Contract - USDA.ARS.AE. Farm Electrification Section (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Research Contract - USDA.ARS.AE. Farm Electrification Section (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Forms, Lists, Graphs, Diagrams & Other Data (Box 10, Folder 36-39)
- Lists & Charts (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Charts (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
- Circular Graphs (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
- Graphs (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Bulk Milk Cooler Field Studies: Individual Reports (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Forms (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
- Reports, 1953-54 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Reports, 1955-57 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Reports, 1958-59 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Reports, 1960-? (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
- Financial Reports (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
- Photographs (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Teaching Report (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Crop Yields (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Untitled (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Economics (Box 11, Folder 22)
- G.E. Brooder (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Lyon Rural Electric Company (Box 11, Folder 24)
- UNICO Research Lab (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Correspondence of Jon Beam Co. to Turner (Box 11, Folder 26)
- In-Service Training for Agricultural Leaders (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Public Service Commission (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Commodity Committee (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Heating Cable at Vet Barn (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Pumping Fixtures (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Molasses Pumping (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Germicidal Radiation (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Marketing Research Project (Watering Poul) (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Post War Planning (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Edison Electric Research Notes (Box 11, Folder 36)
- EEI Handbook (Box 11, Folder 37)
- EEI Annual Records Report (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Electricity: Empire State Gas & Electric Association - Mr. Sloan (Box 11, Folder 39)
- NYS Electric Cooperative Association (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Electricity: Public Service Committee - Mr. Vanneman (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Electrical Equipment Handbook (Box 11, Folder 42)
- NYS Agriculture & Technical Institute (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Time & Travel Studies - Poultry Watering & Vent (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Time And Motion (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Michigan State University (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Untitled (Box 11, Folder 47-48)
- Book Keeping System, 1952-53 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Miscellaneous Matters (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Untitled (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Poultry Watering System - Walter Schait, Dryden (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Untitled (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Hudson Valley Farms, 1929-34 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Electric Brooder F.L.F - Run II (Box 12, Folder 2)
- W.G.Y. Radio Talks, thru 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Electricity on the Farm - "News And Previews", 1937-49 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Electricity on the Farm - "News And Previews", 1950-55 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Deming Pumps (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Information on the Rural Electrification From the Census of Agriculture, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Doane Agricultural service, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Pump and Water Systems School, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 9)